Ryosuke Hujisawa

Full-Stack Developer

interview@off.tokyo Vancouver, BC 236-668-4441

Personal Profile

I have been working for a Full-Stack Developer for 4 years, with my most recent experience being a web developer. My strong point is the "patient". I had a experienced working with a one company on a long-term basis. I want to long-term basis with you.

Work Experience - 1 (Intern)

Apple Corporation Ad inc

January 2014 - December 2015

Key Skills(iOS Developer)

Familiarity with Swift4, perfect(Server-side Swift), Realm, React Native, or any mobile app development. AdMob Mobile Ads Operation

Job Details

I did support of the development team. Implementation of small parts of the iOS application. release and update work to the app store. also, Implementation of mobile application advertisement and operated.

I developed an iOS application individually. It is an iOS game called Rupo Maker. I have development experience with Swift 3 and have experience in publishing on Internet media.

Work Experience - 2 (Full Time)

Apple Corporation Ad inc

January 2016 - March 2018

Key Skills(Web Developer)

Practical understanding of Javascript (ES6, Node.js), HTML5 and CSS, Bootstrap, AJAX, JQuery, and Experienced PHP MAMP and WordPress.

Experience deploying Applications to AWS, Heroku and experience with one or more database systems MySQL

Job Details

We have developed an in-houce reception system used PHP, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3. We used Git for version control and checked our ode. Implemented the notification function using Slack 's API.

We had our main business, advertising and cosmetic online shop. We was involved in the development of an online payment system with Stripe (php).

We organized the in-houce web environment. We changed the environment to AWS and changed the OS to Ubuntu. We managed client data with MySQL.

PERSONAL SIDE ROJECT

 $(2013 \sim 2018)$

Wordtranslate(Translation of sentences into words)

January 2013 - December 2014

Bootstrap, PHP, AWS and Python

Wesound(Music material share like SoundCloud)

February 2015 - December 2017

· WordPress, HTML5 and CSS, JQuery, MySQL, PHP, AWS

Portfolio(My self-introduction site)

January 2018 - June 2018

· Bootstrap, GitHub

World Clock(Specify time and convert)

January 2018 - June 2018

Server-side Swift - Perfect, ubuntu, HTML5, CSS3

Education

 $(2012 \sim 2017)$

Horikoshi High School

March 2012- April 2015

General high school, Science course major

Senshu University Faculty of Computer Science

(Night school for working adult student) March 2015 - April 2017

• A technology foundation of information and computation, Analysis and research of compiler structure, Basic programming with C language

Key Skills

(1997 ~ 2018)

Laugh often Love much Passion for work Dream Big Relationship Music is always